{
    "subject": "Chulalongkorn",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Sunandha_Kumariratana",
    "human_readable": "Chulalongkorn is married to Sunandha Kumariratana.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9433493614196777,
            "question": "Who is married to Sunandha Kumariratana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9419108629226685,
            "question": "To whom is Chulalongkorn married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9397405385971069,
            "question": "Who is Sunandha Kumariratana married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9080299735069275,
            "question": "Is there a known spouse of Chulalongkorn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8780609369277954,
            "question": "What is the name of the person married to Sunandha Kumariratana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8262761831283569,
            "question": "Is Chulalongkorn in a marital relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8068961501121521,
            "question": "What is the name of Chulalongkorn's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8068961501121521,
            "question": "What is the name of Chulalongkorn's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7997757792472839,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the marriage of Chulalongkorn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7770000696182251,
            "question": "Who is associated with Sunandha Kumariratana in a marital relationship?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Chulalongkorn is married to Sunandha Kumariratana.",
            "html": "yago_2901_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the marriage of Chulalongkorn?",
            "html": "yago_2901_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Chulalongkorn's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_2901_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Chulalongkorn's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_2901_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2901_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2901_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2901_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2901_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2901_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2901_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2901_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2901_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2901_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2901_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After reviewing the provided context information, I can determine that:\n\n* The triple statement \"Chulalongkorn is married to Sunandha Kumariratana\" is indeed supported by the documents.\n\nHere's the structured JSON format response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Chulalongkorn is married to Sunandha Kumariratana.\" They mention her as his queen consort and first wife, indicating their marital relationship."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}